<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<teiCorpus xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader/>
  <teiCorpus n="1" xml:id="contemplated">
    <teiHeader/>
    <text/>
    <TEI xml:id="ipfs_content_ids">
      <text>
        <group>
          <text xml:id="active_YYYYMMDDThhmmssZ">
            <body>
              <div n="1">
                <docDate when-iso="20251030"/>
                <post n="1" when-iso="T161723Z">
                  <idno generatedBy="filebase" sortKey="QmTWAmhWsGckNsm3myWmdKfcBKRybuTXPNLUtz2ZA4R2nf"/>
                  <idno generatedBy="pinata" sortKey="bafkreie3jzcbvan6weiw2e3uhoayf74huxnr4kbdt3sfktqdxqbbpfez5m"/>
                  <desc>this very file before adding @when-iso timestamps and @sortKey CIDs</desc>
                </post>
                <post n="2" when-iso="T182837Z" xml:id="priv_20251030T182837Z">
                  <idno generatedBy="filebase" sortKey="QmYtDPfyQeUAFEqHangatPXDwSXC7wj4aj6ccFwYbeE3mv"/>
                  <idno generatedBy="pinata" sortKey="bafkreibmlajsdvpmycxa44bwt7os7lvdhhwvbl263akd73ysm6vk2rqoxi"/>
                  <p>
                    <s>I'm creating this file as place where I can build a story that I don't want exposed to every audience I work with.</s>
                    <s>Yet the nature of the story I'll be trying to build here is very relevant within the scope of a greater project that will have pointers to indicate instances of this more private work aside.</s>
                    <s>The greater project is, at least initially, an attempt to organize my life.</s>
                    <s>For that, I'm working with a few AIs (ChatGPT, DeepSeek, Gemini, Brave's Leo, etc.), some of whom require accounts.</s>
                    <s>
                      My use of the IPFS also uses a few accounts,
                      but their roles if I understand correctly are more to share (pin) files to the IPFS than to environmentally contain them like ordinary Internet file or web hosting services do.
                    </s>
                  </p>
                  <p>
                    <s>I've gotten used to my own interests in life being more personal than transpersonal.</s>
                    <s>
                      Even in my thinking of the world beyond myself I'm thinking of various persons, trying to comprehend what their selves' personal truths might be,
                      and I have found that many people are uncomfortable with that simple of a version of relativity.</s>
                    <s>
                      Some people are even aggressively preventative to this way of relating to human and personal life, and so in order to survive,
                      I've had to seek those persons and those environments that are for whatever reason and in whatever way more tolerant.
                    </s>
                    <s>
                      But even with best effort I'm still having trouble,
                      and so I'm interested in seeing how a more decentralized environment like the IPFS might allow me to work through the kinds of thinking I need for things like mental health.
                    </s>
                    <s>This file is the beginning of that experiment.</s>
                  </p>
                </post>
                <post n="3" when-iso="T195142Z" xml:id="priv_20251030T195142Z">
                  <idno generatedBy="filebase" sortKey="QmYcsMCrMSqorRELjm2rJX5Mbu4MPWRwnmN28UvhTYQVg6"/>
                  <idno generatedBy="pinata" sortKey="bafkreideol3u5i2ktlonbxvhplsstvsmxpmqq723gejpiimlfsvuj7bu4e"/>
                  <p>
                    <s>The practical ordinary environment I live in nowadays in real life seems to be mostly three-fold.</s>
                    <s>
                      Thanks to my Alachua County Community Support Services Permanent Supportive Housing Case Manager Nicole Lee Bartlett and her agency,
                      I have a bed to sleep on at night, a roof over my head, a refrigerator and shower and electricity, etc.
                    </s>
                    <s>
                      Thanks to Gainesville's Bo Diddley Plaza Parks Recreation and Cultural Affairs Recreation Leader Jonathan Michael Gaunt and others like him around the Gainesville area,
                      I have peaceful spaces where I can stop and appreciate nature or recreate and culturalize with other people when those qualities of activity are helpful and appropriate.
                    </s>
                    <s>
                      Thanks to Alachua County Library District's Reference and Genealogy Librarian Caroline Marie Huguet,
                      I feel safe within the library as a space for learning and developing my more intellectual interests.
                    </s>
                  </p>
                  <p>
                    <s>
                      However, within these practicalities I still relate to further social structures like Church and State, and unfortunately,
                      as good as these three persons are in their respective fields with their many helpful coworkers,
                      I relate to them being the local faces of authority who represent not just the better but also often the worse of political institution.
                    </s>
                    <s>Of course it's important to be very careful how we address or even refer to persons we feel political tension in relation to.</s>
                    <s>
                      If we want to progress in life, we want to be at least as helpful as harmful,
                      and given how well-balanced the three persons I'm referencing seem to be, that quality of respect might take some effort.
                    </s>
                    <s>
                      I don't want to make anyone angry by being too chaotically suggestive of wrongdoing nor negligence,
                      so much as my healing process being a very personal variety of forward movement, I need to work through some thoughts and feelings in a meaningfully objective way.
                    </s>
                    <s>So, slowly and attentively to polite detail, I'm going to try to build this and linked pages as expressions of concerns that I believe are valid.</s>
                  </p>
                </post>
              </div>
            </body>
          </text>
        </group>
      </text>
    </TEI>
  </teiCorpus>
</teiCorpus>
